Florence Hollis and Rosemary Ross Reynolds Papers, 1863-1987
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- Series IV. TEACHING
  - Smith College School for Social Work
    - "Casework in Marital Counseling" seminar
      - Case records and notes
        - 1955, ca. 1952-1955 (Box 14, Folder 91)
        - ca. 1956 (Box 14, Folder 92)
        - 1957, ca. 1954-1957 (Box 14, Folder 93)
        - 1961 (Box 14, Folder 94)
    - "Educational Methods in Teaching Casework" seminar
      - Lecture notes
        - ca. 1955-1961 (Box 15, Folder 95)
        - ca. 1956-1961 (Box 15, Folder 96)
        - ca. 1956-1961 (Box 15, Folder 97)
        - ca. 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 98)
        - ca. 1961 (Box 15, Folder 99)
    - "Educational Methods in Teaching Casework" seminar
      - Case books and related materials
        - ca. 1953-1956 (Box 15, Folder 100)
        - ca. 1955 (Box 15, Folder 101)
        - 1957 (Box 15, Folder 102)
        - 1958 (Box 15, Folder 103)
        - 1961 (Box 15, Folder 104)
    - Annette Garrett's courses, student notes, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - Miscellaneous teaching materials
    - Bibliographies
      - ca. 1940-1959 (Box 15, Folder 106)
      - ca. 1961-1971 (Box 15, Folder 107)
    - Case notes and records
      - Philadelphia and Cleveland [?], ca. 1928-1931 (Box 15, Folder 108)
      - Philadelphia and Cleveland, ca. 1932-1937 (Box 16, Folder 109)
      - Philadelphia [?] and Cleveland, ca. 1934-1935 (Box 16, Folder 110)
      - Philadelphia and Cleveland, ca. 1935-1941 (Box 16, Folder 111)
      - Young case, record, committee minutes and memo, used in teaching [?], 1956-1958 (Box 16, Folder 112)
      - Valenti case, notes, used in teaching [?], ca. 1959 (Box 16, Folder 113)
      - Lists of cases used in classes and institutes from ca. 1929 to 1971, ca. 1951-1976, undated (Box 16, Folder 114)
    - Diagnostic-functional issues
      - Diagnostic evaluation guidelines, assorted documents, 1937-1966 (Box 16, Folder 115)
      - Diagnosis and social study, notes, ca. 1940-1955, undated (Box 16, Folder 116)
      - Diagnostic versus functional placements, reports, memos, correspondence and related materials, 1948-1952, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 117)
      - Diagnostic-functional contrasts, assorted materials, ca. 1948-1958, ca. 1985 (Box 16, Folder 118)
      - Lecture notes, ca. 1952, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 119)
      - Lecture notes, ca. 1952-1954, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 120)
    - Institutes, Seminars and Conferences
      - "Family casework," notes and case study, Greenwich Institute conference, June 23-July 3, 1943 (Box 16, Folder 121)
      - Seminar, case records and notes, St. Paul Family Service Agency, ca. 1947-1948 (Box 16, Folder 122)
      - Seminar, notes and case records, St. Paul Family Service Agency, Minneapolis, Minnesota, ca. 1948 (Box 17, Folder 123)
      - Philadelphia Institute, case records and notes, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 17, Folder 124)
      - "Developments in Casework Methodology," program, roster and correspondence, National Institute for Social Work Training, Tavistock Place, London, June 1966 (Box 17, Folder 125)
      - Second International Conference on Psychodynamic Social Work, Smith College, July 27-August 1, 1982
        - Itinerary and correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 126)
        - Notes for plenary session, ca. July 1982 (Box 17, Folder 127)
        - Draft for plenary session [?], ca. July 1982 (Box 17, Folder 128)
        - Cassette recording of plenary session, August 1982 (Box 17, Folder 129)
        - Scraps from the original transcription of the plenary session, August 1982 (Box 17, Folder 130)
        - Plenary session, "last scraps," August 1982 (Box 17, Folder 131)
        - Plenary session, "working sheets," August 1982 (Box 17, Folder 132)
        - Papers and editorial comments, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 133)
      - "Resolved and Unresolved Issues in Social Work Practice," correspondence and course materials, Bryn Mawr College, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 134)
    - Marriage counseling
      - Cleveland study group on marriage counseling, minutes and notes, ca. 1939-1940, 1985 (Box 17, Folder 135)
      - Miscellaneous notes, ca. 194[?]-1976, ca. 1986 (Box 17, Folder 136)
      - Lecture notes, ca. 1949-1969, ca. 1986 (Box 17, Folder 137)
      - Lecture notes and related materials, 1962-1976, ca. 1986 (Box 18, Folder 138)
    - Reading notes
      - A-T, covers 1928-1966, undated (Box 18, Folder 139)
      - A-M, covers 1930-1979, undated (Box 18, Folder 140)
      - O-W, covers 1930-1979, undated (Box 18, Folder 141)
      - According to subject or course, covers 1950-1968 (Box 18, Folder 142)
      - Created ca. 1958-1971
        - A-D, covers 1921-1969, 1971, undated (Box 18, Folder 143)
        - E-G, covers 1915-1970, undated (Box 18, Folder 144)
        - H-L, covers 1917-1970, undated (Box 18, Folder 145)
        - M-P, covers 1939-1970, undated (Box 19, Folder 146)
        - R-S, covers 1942-1969, undated (Box 19, Folder 147)
        - T-Z, covers 1936-1967, undated (Box 19, Folder 148)
      - ca. 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 149)
      - "To read," ca. 1960-1980 (Box 19, Folder 150)
      - Professional journal reading notes, covers 1973-1978 (Box 19, Folder 151)
      - On poverty, multi-problem families and hard to reach families, ca. 1960s (Box 19, Folder 152)
      - "Ideas," newsclippings and notes, ca. 1970-1980 (Box 19, Folder 153)
    - Resource materials
      - Publications by associates, annotated by Florence Hollis, 1930-1956, ca. 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 154)
      - "Interesting papers," 1940-1966, ca. 1980 (Box 19, Folder 155)
      - "Interesting papers," ca. 1967-1976 (Box 20, Folder 156)
      - "Interesting papers," 1978-1983, undated (Box 20, Folder 157)
      - "A Conceptual Framework for Social Casework," Cockerill, et al., School of Social Work, University of Pittsburgh, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 158)
      - "Four Assumptions Underlying Social Work," and "Science, Art, and Social Casework," Louis Lehrman,School of Social Work, University of Pittsburgh, ca. 1957 (Box 20, Folder 159)
      - "Emerging Models of Social Casework Practice," Werner A. Lutz, University of Connecticut School of Social Work, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 160)
    - Supervision
      - Conferences with students, Cleveland and Philadelphia, ca. 1931-1937, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 161)
      - Summaries, conference notes, minutes, Philadelphia Committee on Training for Psychiatric Social Work, ca. 1931-1933 (Box 20, Folder 162)
      - "Objectives, methods," reports, committee notes and related materials, 1934-1947 (Box 20, Folder 163)
      - Seminar, notes and related material, Family Service Association of America, Charlestown, West Virginia, ca. 1935 (Box 20, Folder 164)
      - Seminar, notes, Asilomar, ca. 1950, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 165)
    - Teaching notes
      - "Scattered teaching notes," ca. 1930s (Box 20, Folder 166)
      - "Scattered teaching notes," consultation with Dr. Maider, ca. 1933 (Box 20, Folder 167)
      - "Scattered teaching notes," ca. 1930s (Box 20, Folder 168)
      - "Scattered teaching notes, casework, spiral notebook," ca. 1936-1939, 1985 (Box 20, Folder 169)
      - Notes for teaching or writing, ca. 1958-1960s, undated (Box 20, Folder 170)
- Series V. CASE RECORDS
  - A., Mr.; New York School of Social Work, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Abott, John; New York School of Social Work, 1945-1953 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Abrams, Gladys; New York School of Social Work, course #220, ca. 1960 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Adams, Martha; CW 2, course #122, 1948-1953 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Adams, Raymond and Alice; New York School of Social Work, CW 2 course #122, 1944-1952, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Aged Casebook; New York School of Social Work, 1956-1960 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Alexander; New York School of Social Work, CW 3, course #122, undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Andrews, Stanley; New York School of Social Work, course #123, 1951, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Archer, James and Helen; 1936 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Aryns, Ralph and Catherine; ca. 1948-1950 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - B. Mr.; New York School of Social Work, (from Cleveland MSW), course #220, 1958-1961, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - B. Mrs.; Columbia University School of Social Work, course #T6202, ca. 1966-1967 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Baeder, Elmer and Lelah; 1935-1936, undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Baker; 1936 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Bard, William and Sarah; ca. 1949 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Barker, Raymond and Margaret; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1934-1936 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Bates; 1935 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Beach; CCRA, 1935, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Beaupres; New York School of Social Work, 1954, undated (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Bennington, Oscar and Lucille; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1936-1937, undated (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Benoit, Michael and Florence; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1957-1960 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Berkeley; New York School of Social Work, Course # 124, ca. 1950-1962 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Billings, Russell and Elinore; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1935-1936, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Bjointly, Mr. and Mrs.; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1952-1963 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Braddock, John; New York School of Social Work, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Bradley; AC, 1938, undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Breymaier; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Brown, Ruth; ca. 1938-1940 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Brummer, Charles and Jane; Family Service Association of America, ca. 1963-1970, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Bruno, Nicholas and Marie; 1934, undated (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Burke; Columbia University School of Social Work, ca. 1954-1969, undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Burke, John; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1952 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Burman, Sam and Mary; Family Service Association of America, 1952-ca. 1954 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Burton, Lenard and Laura; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1937-1939, undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - C., Louis; Jewish Guild for the Blind, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - C., Miss; New York School of Social Work, course #220, 1958-1963 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Cadman, Barbara; Fr. Institute of Almoners, London, ca. 1953-1956 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Cafferty, Patrick and Bridget; New York School of Social Work, course #120, ca. 1945-1955, undated (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Caldwell, Joe and Elizabeth; 1936, undated (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Cantor; 1964-1965 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Carey, John and Helen; 1933, undated (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Carlos, Juan and Venita; New York School of Social Work, CW 1, course #120 and course #121, ca. 1942-1957,undated (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Carter, Harold and Myra; New York School of Social Work, course #123, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Case Folder 220; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1958-1959 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Chester, Andrew and Marion; Columbia University School of Social Work, ca. 1962-1966 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Cianco, Anthony and Carmen; Cleveland, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Claus[e]; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, ca. 1940-1942 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Cleveland University Hospital Records; ca. 1963-1965 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Cole, Charles and Elaine; AC and CCRA, 1935-1936, undated (Box 22, Folder 49)
  - Comfort, Harold and Josephine; Family Society of Philadelphia, Philadelphia Study of Marriage Counseling, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - Connocker; Dr. Werner's seminar, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Cord, Mrs.; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1959, undated (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Corke, Clara and Rachel; New York School of Social Work, CW 2, course #121, ca. 1944-1959 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Cornfeld, Samuel; ca. 1960-1970 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Corrigan; CCRA and AC, 1933-1934 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Corsi, Mike; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1951 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Crane, Joseph and Rosemary; Philadelphia Study of Marriage Counseling, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - D. Family (1); ca. 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - D. Family (2); 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - D., Mr.; ca. 1967-1968 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Daly, Ben and Honey; New York School of Social Work, CW 2, ca. 1947-1950 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Damon; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1957, undated (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Dane, Allen and Linda; ca. 1953 (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Danielski, Henry and Helen; Cleveland Study of Young Married Couples, ca. 1940 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Davidson, Nina; Jewish Board of Guardians, New York School of Social Work, course #123, ca. 1953 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Davis; Family Service Association of America, ca. 1960 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Denton, Sarah; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1954 (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Devlin, John and Josephine; Philadelphia Study of Marriage Counseling, ca. 1942 (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Diamond, Edward and Kathleen; undated (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Dorsey; 1969 (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Drake, John and Barbara; St. Louis Institute, ca. 1952 (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - Dumont; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Eckhardt; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Edison, Edward and Isabel; 1936, undated (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Edwards, June; New York School of Social Work, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Eliott, Herbert; ca. 1936-1937 (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Elliott, Robert and Edna; Columbia University School of Social Work, ca. 1960-1969 (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Erin, Laura; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, ca. 1932-1937, undated (Box 24, Folder 78)
  - F. Family; ca. 1964 (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - F., Mrs. (1); School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, ca. 1934-1935, undated (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - F., Mrs. (2); New York School of Social Work, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - F., Mrs. (3); Community Service Society of New York, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 82)
  - Fain, Sidney and Ruth; Family Service Association of America, ca. 1953-1956 (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Felton, Peggy; New York School of Social Work, course #124, ca. 1949-1955 (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - Flint, Milton and Marge; Columbia University School of Social Work, 1963-1964 (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - Ford, Fred and Naomi; 1936-1937, undated (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Fox, Herman and Mary; New York School of Social Work, CW 2, ca. 1946-1948 (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Frey; 1935, undated (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Fuentes, Anita and Ramon; Columbia University School of Social Work, ca. 1963-1966 (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - G. Case; New York School of Social Work, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - G. Family; ca. 1964 (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - G., Harold; New York School of Social Work, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 92)
  - Garcia (1); Cleveland, ca. 1938-1939 (Box 24, Folder 93)
  - Garcia (2); New York School of Social Work, CW 2, course #122, ca. 1948 (Box 24, Folder 94)
  - Garcia (3); 1958-1960 (Box 24, Folder 95)
  - Gary, Charles and June; AC, Cleveland, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 24, Folder 96)
  - Gee, Linda; Columbia University School of Social Work, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 97)
  - Goldsmith, Charles and Rose; Philadelphia, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 24, Folder 98)
  - Gracci, Angelo and Carmen; 1942-1943 (Box 24, Folder 99)
  - Granville, Frederick and Norma; ca. 1949-1950 (Box 24, Folder 100)
  - Gray, David; New York School of Social Work, CW 3 course #123, ca. 1949-1957 (Box 24, Folder 101)
  - Grayson, Norman and Christine; ca. 1933-1937 (Box 25, Folder 102)
  - Green; ca. 1952-1953 (Box 25, Folder 103)
  - Green, Pauline; undated (Box 25, Folder 104)
  - Gruber, Edward; New York School of Social Work, course #121, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 25, Folder 105)
  - Guilford; New York School of Social Work, course #124, ca. 1949-1950 (Box 25, Folder 106)
  - Guisseppe, Mrs. Angelina; New York School of Social Work, CW 1, ca. 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 107)
  - H. Case; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1956-1957 (Box 25, Folder 108)
  - H., Mr. and Mrs.; ca. 1962 (Box 25, Folder 109)
  - H., Mrs. (1); AC, Cleveland, 1934-1937 (Box 25, Folder 110)
  - H., Mrs. (2); New York School of Social Work, ca. 1951-1952 (Box 25, Folder 111)
  - H., Mrs. (3); Columbia University School of Social Work, ca. 1964 (Box 25, Folder 112)
  - Halling, Lyle and Dale; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 113)
  - Hammond, Jesse and Marilee; Columbia University School of Social Work, ca. 1966 (Box 25, Folder 114)
  - Hampton; New York School of Social Work, course #124, ca. 1949-1968, undated (Box 25, Folder 115)
  - Harris, Benjamin; New York School of Social Work, CW 2, course #122, ca. 1953-1959 (Box 25, Folder 116)
  - Harris, William and Elizabeth; CCRA, 1933-1936, undated (Box 25, Folder 117)
  - Hart, Richard and Emma; New York School of Social Work, 1950 (Box 25, Folder 118)
  - Hartman, Ralph; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 119)
  - Hawkins; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 25, Folder 120)
  - Heinemann, David and Harriet; New York School of Social Work, ca. 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 121)
  - Helle, Jean; New York School of Social Work, undated (Box 25, Folder 122)
  - Helm, Mrs.; "A City Acts to Help the Aging: The Advocacy Role of the Social Worker," ca. 1968 (Box 25, Folder 123)
  - Hinkleman; Cleveland, 1933, undated (Box 25, Folder 124)
  - Holmberg; Lloyd and Emma, University of Minnesota, 1938-1939, undated (Box 25, Folder 125)
  - Honen, Ella; AC, Cleveland, 1935-1936, undated (Box 26, Folder 126)
  - Howard; New York School of Social Work, course #220, ca. 1952-1955, undated (Box 26, Folder 127)
  - Howe; Joseph and Anna, 1933, undated (Box 26, Folder 128)
  - Humphrey; Alex and Maud, CCRA (Rosemary Reynold's case), 1935-1936, undated (Box 26, Folder 129)
  - J., Mr.; New York School of Social Work, 1951-1952, undated (Box 26, Folder 130)
  - Jacino, Jim; New York School of Social Work, 1954-1956 (Box 26, Folder 131)
  - Jane; AC, Cleveland, 1934?, undated (Box 26, Folder 132)
  - Jeffries, Edward; Cleveland, 1935-1936 (Box 26, Folder 133)
  - Jenkins, Frank and Dorothy; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1940, undated (Box 26, Folder 134)
  - Joe; New York School of Social Work, undated (Box 26, Folder 135)
  - Johnson; 1967-1971, undated (Box 26, Folder 136)
  - Johnson, Helen; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1940?, undated (Box 26, Folder 137)
  - Johnson, Mr.; New York School of Social Work, course #220, 1953, undated (Box 26, Folder 138)
  - Johnson, Wayne and Margaret; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, 1940 (Box 26, Folder 139)
  - Jones, Kenneth and Margaret; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, ca. 1940 (Box 26, Folder 140)
  - K., Mrs. and O., Mrs.; New York School of Social Work, course #220, 1951-1953, undated (Box 26, Folder 141)
  - Kamp, Lewis and Mary; 1934, undated (Box 26, Folder 142)
  - Kaplin, Murray; New York School of Social Work, CW 2, course #122, ca. 1954-1955 (Box 26, Folder 143)
  - Kasentis, John and Koula; Community Service Society, New York, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 144)
  - Kasmerski; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, 1939-1940, undated (Box 26, Folder 145)
  - Katz, Robert; New York School of Social Work, 1953-1954 (Box 26, Folder 146)
  - Kaye, Mr.; Pennsylvania School of Social Work, 1935, undated (Box 26, Folder 147)
  - Kelly, Alice; Columbia University School of Social Work, 1962-1965 (Box 26, Folder 148)
  - Kelly, Grace; New York School of Social Work, 1954 (Box 26, Folder 149)
  - Kelly, Mr.; New York School of Social Work, CW 6, ca. 1950-1951 (Box 26, Folder 150)
  - Kent; New York School of Social Work, 1958-1963, undated (Box 26, Folder 151)
  - Kerner; New York School of Social Work, course #120, 1954-1956, undated (Box 26, Folder 152)
  - Kieffer, Douglas and Grace; Philadelphia Study of Marriage Counseling and Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, 1942, undated (Box 26, Folder 153)
  - Killian; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, 1940, undated (Box 26, Folder 154)
  - Killian, Elizabeth; 1939-1940, undated (Box 27, Folder 155)
  - Kimball, Robert and Ruth (Kallisch, Paul and Marie); New York School of Social Work, course #124 and course #128, 1948-1950, undated (Box 27, Folder 156)
  - Koran, Joseph and Mary; CCRA, Cleveland, 1935-1936 (Box 27, Folder 157)
  - Kraemer; Cleveland FS, 1939-1940, undated (Box 27, Folder 158)
  - Krause, Charles and Lena; CCRA, Cleveland, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 159)
  - Krinowski, Michael and Mary; AC, Cleveland, 1933 (Box 27, Folder 160)
  - Kronin; 1934, undated (Box 27, Folder 161)
  - Krupa, Alex and Sadie; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, 1940 (Box 27, Folder 162)
  - Kumlar; AC, Cleveland, 1933-1935, undated (Box 27, Folder 163)
  - Kyrian; AC, Cleveland, 1935, undated (Box 27, Folder 164)
  - L. Family; New York School of Social Work, course #124, 1952-1959, undated (Box 27, Folder 165)
  - L., Mr. and Mrs.; 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 166)
  - L. Record; New York School of Social Work, 1951-1952, undated (Box 27, Folder 167)
  - Landers; New York School of Social Work, course #123, 1953-1954, undated (Box 27, Folder 168)
  - Landon; New York School of Social Work, course #124, 1952-1955, undated (Box 27, Folder 169)
  - Lane, John and Mary; New York School of Social Work, CW 1, 1950-1955, undated (Box 27, Folder 170)
  - Lansing, Horace and Lelia; New York School of Social Work, CW 2, 1942-1955, undated (Box 27, Folder 171)
  - Lee; New York School of Social Work, 1956-1957, undated (Box 27, Folder 172)
  - Lewis, Anna; New York School of Social Work, CW 3, course #123, 1948-1953, undated (Box 27, Folder 173)
  - L'Hota; CCRA, Cleveland, 1936, undated (Box 27, Folder 174)
  - Linton, Larry and Rhoda; 1930, undated (Box 27, Folder 175)
  - Lister, Theodore and Sally; Philadelphia Study of Marriage Counseling, 1942, undated (Box 27, Folder 176)
  - Long; New York School of Social Work, 1952-1962, undated (Box 27, Folder 177)
  - M., Irene; Summer Institute, St. Vincent's Hospital of the City of New York, 1950-1952, undated (Box 28, Folder 178)
  - M., Johnny; New York School of Social Work, 1955, undated (Box 28, Folder 179)
  - M., Miss; New York School of Social Work, (medical social work) course #220, 1953-1954, undated (Box 28, Folder 180)
  - M., Mr.; New York School of Social Work, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 181)
  - Mahler; 1946, undated (Box 28, Folder 182)
  - Malara, Frank and Gertrude; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1933, undated (Box 28, Folder 183)
  - Marcus; New York School of Social Work, 1951-1952, undated (Box 28, Folder 184)
  - Marsh, Henry and Elizabeth; New York School of Social Work, course #124, 1935-1950, undated (Box 28, Folder 185)
  - Martin, Bobbie; New York School of Social Work, (medical social work), course #222, 1953, undated (Box 28, Folder 186)
  - Mary; School of Applied Social Sciences, Western Reserve University, 1932-1935, undated (Box 28, Folder 187)
  - McAllister, Katherine; 1936, undated (Box 28, Folder 188)
  - McKinley; New York School of Social Work, course #128, 1947-1957, undated (Box 28, Folder 189)
  - Meisterics, John and Mary; Cleveland Study of Marriage Counseling, 1940, undated (Box 28, Folder 190)
  - Melnick, Jeanne; Philadelphia FS, 1935, undated (Box 28, Folder 191)
  - Meltzer, Mrs.; New York School of Social Work, 1950, undated (Box 28, Folder 192)
  - Mendez; Columbia University School of Social Work, 1965-1966, undated (Box 28, Folder 193)
  - Miller, Myron; Columbia University School of Social Work,1956-1971, undated (Box 28, Folder 194)
  - Miller, Raymond and Elsie; 1933, undated (Box 28, Folder 195)
  - Milton; New York School of Social Work, 1956-1957, undated (Box 28, Folder 196)